getpaidfasttoday.com 2017-08-14

# Privacy | Advertise Out Marketing News

AdvertiseOut.com (“AdvertiseOut.com “, “we” or “us”), respects the privacy of visitors to its website, the home page of which is located at http://www.AdvertiseOut.com Wealth.com (the “Website”), and affiliated websites and is committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of your personal information. This privacy policy explains how we collect, use, disclose and safeguard the personal information you provide to us.

AdvertiseOut.com is a publisher of financial news and opinions and NOT securities brokers/dealers or investment advisors. You are responsible for your own investment decisions. All information contained in our newsletters or on our web site(s) should be independently verified with the companies mentioned, and readers should always conduct their own research and due diligence and consider obtaining professional advice before making any investment decision. As a condition to accessing our materials and web sites, you agree to our Disclaimer available [HERE](http://wealth.advertiseout.com%20.com/disclaimer/ "Disclaimer"), and Terms of Use available [HERE](http://wealth.advertiseout.com%20.com/terms/ "General Terms and Conditions of Use"), including without limitation all disclaimers of warranties and limitations on liability contained therein. Owners, employees and writers may hold positions in the securities that are discussed in our newsletters or on our web site. 

By providing personal information to us, and by submitting personal information through the Website, you signify your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. By submitting your information via our website or one of our partners, and requesting information or a quote or free report from us, you acknowledge and agree that a provider may contact you using your information to provide your requested quote or to obtain additional information needed to provide your requested quotes where permitted by law. In the event that we do not have a provider, your information may be shared with another company that will provide this same or related services. This company may have several providers contact you at their discretion. We are not responsible, and shall not be held liable, if a Provider or other third party to whom we have forwarded any of the information you submitted to us violates our Privacy Policy or such third party’s own privacy policy (if any), or otherwise violates the law.

The United States federal private sector privacy legislation, the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, and the protection of personal information in the private sector, are the basis for AdvertiseOut.com ‘s privacy policy.

For purposes of this privacy policy, “personal information” shall mean any information that can identify an individual directly or through other reasonably available means.

As part of our commitment to treat your personal information with respect, we operate in accordance with the following ten principles (the “Principles”):

1\. Accountability

2\. Identifying Purposes

3\. Consent

4\. Limiting Collection

5\. Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention

6\. Accuracy

7\. Safeguarding Information

8\. Openness

9\. Individual Access

10\. Handling Complaints and Suggestions

Principle 1 – Accountability

We will maintain and protect the personal information under our control. We have policies and procedures for ensuring privacy and security of data which are strictly enforced to protect the individuals from whom we collect personal information. To that end, we have designated a Privacy Officer, to be accountable for compliance with the Principles and this privacy policy. Please see Principle 10, below, to obtain the contact information for our Privacy Officer.

When we use trusted third parties to act on our behalf by performing such functions as processing credit card payments, contractual or other appropriate means are used to ensure compliance by such third parties with this privacy policy and all applicable privacy laws.

Principle 2 – Identifying Purposes

AdvertiseOut.com will identify to you the purposes for which we will collect or use personal information before or at the time the information is collected.

We collect personal information that you submit to us voluntarily through the Website.

We collect and use the personal information of users of our Website (“Users” or “you”), in order to:

▪ Process and fulfill your request to register as a user of the Website.

▪ Register, develop, maintain and operate “Your Profile”.

▪ Process service and information requests.

▪ Process feedback and comments.

▪ Provide you with information regarding the services offered through our Website.

▪ Enable you to participate in online journals, testimonials, groups, or message boards. Personally identifiable consumer information collected to process your request, might include contact information such as name, mailing address, telephone number and email address. All customer’s information we collect is strictly confidential and maintained in electronic files. Our participating advertisers and affiliates, to whom this information is referred, are bound by the same terms of confidentiality, and use such information to contact the customers for purposes of providing customers with the requested quotes and information. AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites cannot control what Advertisers subsequently do with that information.

▪ Personalize the delivery of content and information.

▪ Send you notices and information on other products and services that we believe may be of interest to you.

▪ Register you for conferences, and send you information pertaining to such conferences.

Some of the personal information you entered into your AdvertiseOut.com profile and any information, including personal information, that you enter using one of these features, might be used and displayed.

Unless otherwise permitted or required by law, if a new purpose is identified for the use of the information collected, the new purpose will be explained prior to its new use.

Principle 3 – Consent

Except where required or permitted by law your informed consent is required for our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information.

By providing personal information to us, you signify your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Principle 4 – Limiting Collection

AdvertiseOut.com will identify to you the purposes for which it will use personal information before or at the time the personal information is collected. The types of personal information we may collect depends on and is related to the reason (or purpose) such personal information was provided to us.

What Sort of Personal Information May We Collect?:

The following is a non-exhaustive description of the types of personal information that we may request or collect from Users:

▪ Contact information, such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address, home telephone and cell phone number.

▪ Demographic information, such as your age and gender.

▪ Profile data

▪ Payment information (e.g. credit card).

The choice to provide us with your personal information is always yours. However, your decision to withhold particular information may result in limiting our ability to provide you with the services or products you have requested.

Please be aware that any information that is publicly posted throughout the Website can be accessed by every visitor of the Website.

How We Collect Your Personal Information?:

We may gather personal information from you in person, over the telephone or by corresponding with you via mail, facsimile or the Internet. We also collect personal information from Users when Users register their profile, view items throughout the Website, complete online order forms and carry out transactions through use of our Website.

Personal Information Collected via Technology:

As you navigate the Website, certain non-personal information may be passively collected and stored on our Internet server logs, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Website you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor your experience on the Website to meet your special interests and needs.

What are Cookies: Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using the Website easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Website, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. (Note: you will need to consult the help area of your browser application for instructions.) If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of the Website will not function properly or may be considerably slower.

What are IP Addresses: An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you’re surfing the Internet. When you request pages from the Website, our servers log your IP address. AdvertiseOut.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of the Website. We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the law, our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Website, Users, or others. Other third parties may place advertisements and cookies on webpages within the Website. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

Principle 5 – Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention

We will only use or disclose your personal information in accordance with the purposes for which it was originally collected unless you have otherwise consented, or when it is required or permitted by law. We will retain your personal information only for so long as is required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected or as required by law.

When Information May Be Disclosed to Outside Parties:

Except as explained in this privacy policy, as otherwise consented to by you or permitted by law, we do not disclose any personal information to third parties. The following are the limited instances where we may disclose your personal information to third parties:

Participating Partners and Advertisers. Personally identifiable consumer information collected to process your request, might include contact information such as name, mailing address, telephone number and email address. All customer’s information we collect is strictly confidential and maintained in electronic files. Our participating partners, advertisers and affiliates, to whom this information is referred, are bound by the same terms of confidentiality, and may use such information to contact the customers for purposes of providing customers with the requested quotes.

Principle 6 – Accuracy

We shall make every reasonable effort to ensure your personal information is maintained in an accurate, complete and up-to-date form. You are responsible for advising AdvertiseOut.com of any inaccuracies or changes to your personal information.

Principle 7 – Safeguarding Information

The security of your personal information is a priority to us. AdvertiseOut.com is responsible for protecting personal information under its control, including personal information that has been transferred to, or received from, a third party.

In the event that personal information is transferred to a third party, AdvertiseOut.com will take steps to ensure that such recipients safeguard the personal information and use the information only for authorized purposes. Some examples of such measures are as follows:

▪ Physical security measures such as restricted access facilities and locked filing cabinets.

▪ Electronic security measures for computerized personal information such as password protection, database encryption and personal identification numbers.

▪ Organizational processes such as limiting access to such personal information to a selected group of individuals.

▪ Contractual obligations with third parties who need access to personal information by agreements stipulating the confidentiality of the information and requiring them to protect and secure the personal information.

▪ When credit card information is transmitted via our Web Site we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

We manage our server environment appropriately and our firewall infrastructure is strictly adhered to. Our security practices are reviewed on a regular basis and we routinely employ current technologies to ensure that the confidentiality and privacy of your information is not compromised.

Only employees with a business need to know, or whose duties reasonably so require, are granted access to personal information and shall be required to respect the privacy of that information.

When you call us you may be required to verify your identity by providing some personally identifying information.

Our Employees and your Personal Information:

In the course of daily operations, access to private, sensitive and confidential information is restricted to authorized employees who have a legitimate business purpose and reason for accessing it. For example, when you call us, our designated employees will access your information to verify who you are and to assist you in fulfilling your requests.

As a condition of their employment, all employees of AdvertiseOut.com are required to abide by the privacy standards we have established. Employees are informed about the importance of privacy and they are required to agree to a code of conduct that prohibits the disclosure of any customer information to unauthorized individuals or parties.

Unauthorized access to and/or disclosure of personal information by an employee of AdvertiseOut.com is strictly prohibited. All employees are expected to maintain the confidentiality of personal information at all times and failing to do so will result in appropriate disciplinary measures, which may include dismissal.

Principle 8 – Openness

If you would like a copy of our privacy policy we would be more than happy to provide one to you and if you have any questions regarding same, we are more than happy to discuss the merits with you.

Principle 9 – Individual Access

Upon your request, we shall inform you of: (i) the types of personal information we have collected; (ii) how we have used your personal information in the past, and how we may in the future; and (iii) whether or not we have disclosed your personal information to any third parties (and, if so, to whom). Individuals may verify the accuracy and completeness of their personal information, and may request that it be amended, if appropriate.

To help us keep your personal information up-to-date, we encourage you to amend inaccuracies and make corrections as often as necessary. Despite our efforts, errors sometimes do occur. Should you identify any incorrect or out-of-date information in your file(s), we will make the proper changes. Where appropriate, we will communicate these changes to other parties who may have unintentionally received incorrect information from us. Please note that before we are able to provide you with any information or correct any inaccuracies we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help us to respond to your request.

You may access and verify any of your information by calling 480-428-0847 or writing to our Privacy Officer at [info@AdvertiseOut.com .com](mailto:info@AdvertiseOut.com%20.com)

Principle 10 – Handling Complaints and Suggestions

You may direct any questions, complaints or enquiries with respect to the Principles, this privacy policy or about our information handling practices by contacting:

Updates July 2012

**1\. What Information Do We Collect?**  
a. All Users must provide the following information in order to join AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites: email address. Users may be required to provide subsequent demographic information in order to receive advertiser offers and/or qualify for other promotions. Demographic information includes, but is not limited to: Name, Address, birth date, gender, marital status, and household information.

**2\. How Do We Collect the Information?**  
a. Users may join AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated or partner sites by completing one of our signup forms, through Co-Registration, or other means as we may determine at any time in the future.

**3\. How Do we Use the Information?**  
a. User information is used by AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites in all of the following ways:  
b. E-Mail Address and other information is used to send paid email advertisements and important announcements about AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites to Users  
c. Demographic and other information is used to target advertisements to User including reverse append.  
d. User information may be sold or disclosed to third parties as described in Sections 4 and 6 below  
e. Cookies or similar tracking technology may be used as described in Section 8 below  
f. Information may be used in additional ways as posted on this Privacy Policy in the future.

**4\. How Do We Share the Information?**  
a. AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites does not rent, sell, or share User information, except in the following circumstances:  
b. We are required to release User information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes  
c. Part or all of our business is sold to, merged with, or acquired by another company, in which case some or all User information would then belong to said company  
d. We share User information with partners, advertisers and affiliates when co-registration boxes (explained below) are checked during the course of registration or user elect to receive information or offers.  
e. We suspect a User of committing fraud, in which case User information may be shared during the course of our investigation  
f. We may sell or share User information to other advertisers or businesses whom we believe you may find useful and in order to enhance the service provided to our Users  
g. We may share User information with third parties as reasonably necessary for us to operate this website and to provide offers and services to Users  
h. California Residents Only: If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: (i) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you for the company’s direct marketing purposes; and (ii) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing to Customer Service using the contact information provided Section 10 of this Privacy Policy.  
**5\. What is Co-Registration?**  
a. AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites signup pages may contain co-registration checkboxes, where Users can choose to co-registration for other Web Sites during their registration with AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites by accepting or by checking the checkbox next to the co-registration Offer. Users are not required to keep selected any co-registration boxes to join AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites; however, they may be required to do so in order to qualify for promotions.

**6\. How Do We Share Co-Registration Information?**  
a. When a User co-registers for an Offer by checking, or leaving checked, the co-registration checkbox, any information they provide to AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites may be shared with the Advertiser, partner of affiliate associated with the co-registration Offer. AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites cannot control what Advertisers subsequently do with that information.

Co-Registration Privacy Policy: Under no circumstance will we ever pass any of your information along to anyone unless you specifically request us to do so by selecting or leaving selected the check box next to an offer on our co-registration platform or offer pages and submitting the form. AdvertiseOut.com provides a simple and hassle-free “opt-out” link that lets you conveniently unsubscribe from future emails and offers. AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites cannot control what Advertisers subsequently do with that information.

Co-Registration Data Use Policy for the opt-in offers served served by AdvertiseOut.com .

Below we explain exactly how your data may be used with regard to our co-reg offer (advertising) pages.

In order to target the offers on advertising pages appropriately, the publisher, in accordance with its Privacy Policy, may have passed some of your non-personally identifiable, previously-entered, information such as zip code, gender, age etc., to AdvertiseOut.com . AdvertiseOut.com does not know any of your personally identifiable information. If and only if you confirm the selection of each offer on this page by agreeing to and claiming the opt-in on the associated offer button (Opt-In Button), and then submitting , will AdvertiseOut.com be passed your personally identifiable information by the web publisher.

The 2 ways your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information can be collected are: 1) by the web publisher who’s site you are currently visiting and 2) by entering data on this page directly related to this offer.

For each offer you chose to opt-in to, your personally identifiable information will be passed to AdvertiseOut.com and AdvertiseOut.com will in turn pass it to the corresponding advertiser, along with your non-personally identifiable information. In accordance with each advertiser’s Privacy Policy (see advertiser’s unique offer associated website Privacy Policy for details) The advertiser may then chose to reach out and communicate with you directly. All AdvertiseOut.com advertisers are required under contract to have an unsubscribe mechanism.

**7\. Privacy on Other Sites**  
a. This website may contain links to third party websites. We provide these links for your convenience; we do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other websites is subject to the terms and conditions of those websites, including the privacy policies of those websites.

**8\. About Cookies and Third Party Technology.**  
a. A Cookie is a small data file that may be saved to and stored on your computer when you visit a website or open an email. Cookies permit a website to remember whether your computer has visited the website before and help the website create a more personalized experience for you and records activities taken by you, such as offers completed.  
b. In addition to cookie technology, AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites and our Advertisers use additional third party technology and tracking tools to record offers and activities completed by you, friends referred by you, and to communicate information about you, such as demographic information (e.g., age, gender), in order to target offers and advertisements to specific groups as requested by Advertisers. Cookies and other tracking technology is collectively referred to as cookies and Recording Tools.  
c. Your computer permits you to change the settings on your web browser to not accept and/or disable Cookies and Recording Tools. However, if you do not accept Cookies and Recording Tools used by AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites and our Advertisers, you may not be able to use certain functions on certain websites. More importantly, if you do not accept Cookies and Recording Tools you will not receive credit for offers or other actions completed by you because we and our Advertisers are unable to track and record your activity. If you do not want to accept Cookies and Recording Tools, you must stop using this website.

**9\. Referral and Affiliate Tracking**  
a. AdvertiseOut.com and our affiliated sites uses cookies in order to track new User registrations. This ensures Users are properly credited for referring other Users, as well as to track earnings for our Affiliates.

**10\. Contact us**  
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you, or with to access, delete your information, wish to request information pursuant to Section II.2.(f) of this Privacy Policy, please email us at info@AdvertiseOut.com .com and our affiliated sites.com or send us a letter by first class postage prepaid U.S. mail or overnight courier to the address below.

AdvertiseOut.com is a division of Zenect LLC  
2487 S. Gilbert Rd.  
Suite 106-626  
Gilbert, Arizona 85295  
By Email: [info@AdvertiseOut.com](mailto:info@AdvertiseOut.com)  
Web:http://www.AdvertiseOut.com

Web Sites Governed by this Privacy Policy:

The Website that is governed by the provisions and practices stated in this privacy policy is www.AdvertiseOut.com .com

The Website may contain links to other third party sites that are not governed by this privacy policy. Although we endeavor to only link to sites with high privacy standards, our privacy policy will no longer apply once you leave the Website. Additionally, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other third party websites. Therefore, we suggest that you examine the privacy statements of those websites to learn how your information may be collected, used, shared and disclosed.

Regarding Children:

We do not intentionally gather personal information about visitors who are under the age of 13. IF YOU ARE A PERSON UNDER THE AGE OF 13, WE ASK THAT YOU PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR WEBSITE AND PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE TO US ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION. THE SERVICES ARE INTENDED SOLELY FOR ACCESS AND USE BY INDIVIDUALS THAT ARE at least 18 years old. If you are at least THIRTEEN (13) YEARS OF AGE BUT YOUNGER THAN 18,, you may use the AdvertiseOut.com services if you have your parents’ or guardians’ prior permission. By clicking the “ACCEPT” button you are representing that you are at least 18, or that you are at least 13 years old and have your parents’ permission to register for the services.

Updating this Privacy Policy:

Any changes to our privacy policy and information handling practices will be acknowledged in this policy in a timely manner. We may add, modify or remove portions of this policy when we feel it is appropriate to do so. You may determine when this policy was last updated by referring to the modification date found at the bottom of this privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy, and all related matters are governed solely by the laws of Arizona, USA and applicable federal laws of the United States, excluding any rules of private international law or the conflict of laws which would lead to the application of any other laws.

Last revised June 2014
